Introducing the first documentary re-enactment
true story of the man behind the car
Framing John DeLorean is a documentary, drama film directed by Don Argott.
A documentary interspersed with acted scenes, this portrait of John DeLorean covers the
brilliant but tragically flawed automaker's rise to stardom and shocking down fall.
John DeLorean, played by Alec Baldwin.
Cristina Ferrare, played by Morena Baccarin.
Bill Collins, played by Josh Charles.
John Valestra, played by Dean Winters.
Jim Hoffman, played by Michael Rispoli.
Jerry West, played by Jason Jones.
Framing John DeLorean is a 2019 American documentary
film directed by Don Argott and Sheena M.
Joyce and written by Dan Greeney and Alexandra
Orton, about the life of John DeLorean.
The film stars Alec Baldwin, Morena Baccarin, Josh Charles,
Dean Winters, Michael Rispoli and Jason Jones.
The film was released on June 7, 2019, by Sundance Selects.
While the film is structured as a documentary with a number of involved people as interview subjects,
the film also features reenactments of certain important scenes of DeLorean's story.
It also features behind the scenes footage of the participants of the reenactment scenes
with the cast and crew, who provide their views on DeLorean out-of-character.
The film explores themes of court case, fbi,
engineering, drug trade, muscle car.
The tone is emotional.